human problem
and Alex today is seventy eight
Who is Alex
I don't know if it was Alex
haha
Post Juninho
good afternoon
boyish
my followers
place details
thank you boyish
good afternoon there
1 hug
you don't know the feeling
to put these chairs here in this shed
knowing they are with people
old sky bro
is very different
looks like I'm giving a good guy
I still have eleven places
to be filled
then I was thinking
how can i fill these vacancies
in a faster way,
man
some people sometimes don't have the pix
I will send a payment link
I'll show you exactly how it works
enter here on the bench o
just click payment link
and then you put the value of excellence
ninety seven real
now you select
the installment method
already have the fee here
right o
and i put the option in three times if the person wants
came here for my workshop
and then you just put
continues
just put the person's name
create payment link
copy link
and ready
now i can send this payment link to person
it makes it too easy
because if the person wants to pay on the card
here is the payment link from Cora bank
haha
non-human
I just did the biggest stupid thing
that you can imagine bro
wants to see o
sixty chairs
had nine spaces
yes or link
easy bank payment
Cora guesses uncle
sold everything and more than capacity
now i need to order more
chair
sold out
big ran out
and then man
is nervous
of course i don't think so
but I'm happy to see you
most important is this
take advantage of the process
let's go
the average